<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>elm-conf US 2017</title>
    <link>https://2017.elm-conf.us/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on elm-conf US 2017</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 16:06:35 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://2017.elm-conf.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Call For Proposals Opens April 10, 2017</title>
      <link>https://2017.elm-conf.us/news/cfp-opens-april-10-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 16:06:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2017.elm-conf.us/news/cfp-opens-april-10-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The elm-conf call for proposals (CFP) period opens April 10, 2017.
This is when you can submit a talk for inclusion in the conference.
Submissions will be evaluated blindly by a small panel.
Accepted speakers will get a ticket to the conference, lodging, and travel assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it&amp;rsquo;s your first time proposing a talk, don&amp;rsquo;t worry!
We&amp;rsquo;ll provide a round of feedback for all talks submitted before the last three days of the CFP period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, here are some resources for writing good talk proposals:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dave.cheney.net/2017/02/12/how-to-write-a-successful-conference-proposal&#34;&gt;Dave Cheney: How to Write a Successful Conference Proposal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And some tips from &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/sarahmei/status/821924554779955200&#34;&gt;Sarah Mei&lt;/a&gt;, reproduced here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My #1 conf talk description tip: no first-person sentences.
&amp;ldquo;You will learn&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;I will teach.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;You will see&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;I will show.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Show reviewers that you&amp;rsquo;re consciously putting yourself in the place of the audience, and asking yourself: what they want to learn?
When the talk description is about what the speaker will do, it&amp;rsquo;s usually a shitty talk because the speaker can&amp;rsquo;t detach from their own viewpoint.
I don&amp;rsquo;t want talks where the speaker wants to &lt;em&gt;show&lt;/em&gt; something; I want talks where the speaker wants to &lt;em&gt;teach&lt;/em&gt; something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The difference between show and teach is how much responsibility the speaker takes for helping the audience understand.
&amp;ldquo;You will learn X&amp;rdquo; isn&amp;rsquo;t asserting an outcome&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s helping the audience imagine what they could walk out knowing that they don&amp;rsquo;t know now.
It connects to people in a more visceral way than &amp;ldquo;I will show X,&amp;rdquo; and invests them in your success as a speaker.
Using &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;we will explore&amp;rdquo;) similarly signals reviewers that you&amp;rsquo;re thinking of the audience, and can feel more collaborative than &amp;ldquo;you.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The three overarching goals of removing first person from a talk description:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help you, as the speaker, frame the talk around what the audience wants to learn instead of what you want to show.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Signal folks reviewing the proposal that you&amp;rsquo;re already thinking about how their audience will get what they want from your talk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connect with potential audience members &amp;amp; get them excited about what they&amp;rsquo;ll learn if they go to your talk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This last one is most important for a multi-track conference, but can also help sell tickets even if the conf is a single track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>