<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on elm-conf US 2017</title>
    <link>https://www.elm-conf.us/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on elm-conf US 2017</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 08:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.elm-conf.us/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Speakers Announced</title>
      <link>https://www.elm-conf.us/news/lineup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.elm-conf.us/news/lineup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce the 2017 elm-conf speaker lineup.
It&amp;rsquo;s a wonderful mix of veteran and new speakers across a wide variety of topics.
Our full speaker lineup and full schedule can be found on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.elm-conf.us/talks/&#34;&gt;the talks page&lt;/a&gt;, or you can &lt;a href=&#34;webcal://www.elm-conf.us/talks/index.ics&#34;&gt;add our calendar to your schedule&lt;/a&gt; for the most up-to-date information as we get closer to September 28.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be recording all the talks and making them available online thanks to our kind sponsors at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.elm-conf.us/sponsors/ableton/&#34;&gt;Ableton&lt;/a&gt;.
Thanks to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.elm-conf.us/sponsors/futurice/&#34;&gt;Futurice&lt;/a&gt; we will have live captioning at the venue on the day of the conference.
A huge thank you to both sponsors for helping us make elm-conf more accessible to everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Registration for elm-conf opens Thursday, June 8 at 10AM Central Time.
You will &lt;a href=&#34;https://thestrangeloop.com/register.html&#34;&gt;buy a ticket through Strange Loop&amp;rsquo;s registration&lt;/a&gt;, but it is not necessary to attend Strange Loop to attend elm-conf.
If you do want to attend both events be prepared to buy tickets quickly as Strange Loop usually sells out in under an hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call For Proposals Open Through May 12</title>
      <link>https://www.elm-conf.us/news/cfp-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.elm-conf.us/news/cfp-open/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 2017 elm-conf US Call for Proposals is now open!
This is when you can submit a talk for inclusion in the conference.
Submit your talks at &lt;a href=&#34;https://cfp.elm-conf.us/events/elm-conf-us-2017&#34;&gt;cfp.elm-conf.us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s how this is going to go down:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From &lt;strong&gt;April 10&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;May 12&lt;/strong&gt; you can submit a proposal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you submit before &lt;strong&gt;May 8&lt;/strong&gt;, we will give you one round of feedback on your proposal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We aim to have acceptance notifications sent out by &lt;strong&gt;June 2&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once we have a full schedule and alternates, we will notify everybody who didn&amp;rsquo;t make it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proposals will be evaluated anonymously by a small panel. We won&amp;rsquo;t see names or bios until later in the process. First time speakers, here&amp;rsquo;s your chance to shine. Seasoned veterans: bring your A-game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We expect to have a fair number of submissions, and we only have a limited number of spots (elm-conf US is a single track conference so nobody misses a thing.) Please don&amp;rsquo;t let this keep you from applying! Last year we were able to get a great mix of veteran speakers and new voices on our stage, and we hope to repeat that this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accepted speakers will receive, in addition to their speaking slot, tickets to elm-conf and Strange Loop, lodging, and travel booking. If you are coming from within the continental United States, we&amp;rsquo;ll be able to cover your travel totally. Otherwise, we will provide you a stipend of $550 for your flights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call For Proposals Opens April 10, 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.elm-conf.us/news/cfp-opens-april-10-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 16:06:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.elm-conf.us/news/cfp-opens-april-10-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The elm-conf call for proposals (CFP) period opens April 10, 2017.
This is when you can submit a talk for inclusion in the conference.
Submissions will be evaluated blindly by a small panel.
Accepted speakers will get a ticket to the conference, lodging, and travel assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it&amp;rsquo;s your first time proposing a talk, don&amp;rsquo;t worry!
We&amp;rsquo;ll provide a round of feedback for all talks submitted before the last week of the CFP period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>